Hi, my name's Chandler.
I just moved in next door.
Would you like to battle me
in a post-apocalyptic world...
for control of the galaxy's
last remaining energy source?
Sure, neighbor! Come on in!
Is Janine around?
She's at dance class.
Can I check my room?
Don't go through her stuff.
She gets really mad.
Oh, my God!
It's like a guy never lived in here.
You gotta be careful. This girl
thing is dangerous. It's spreading.
It is?
Is this your pretty pink pillow
on the couch?
Is that your tiny little box that's
too small to put anything in?
Okay, this is not good.
You are a guy, okay?
This is a "guy's" place.
Soon, you'll be soaking
your fingers in stuff.
And your head's gonna be under a big,
brown, drying, big, drying.. It's not good.
-You're right. I'll talk to her.
-Talk to her. Be a man!
-I'm a man.
-Defend yourself!
We have to hem the new dust ruffle.
Be right there, sweetums.
Totally different situation.
The One With Ross' Teeth
Hey, guys.
-How was breakfast with Hillary?
-Okay.
She's still depressed because
she broke up with her boyfriend.
Is this Hillary, your
hot assistant chef, Hillary?
The one that stares at me
when I come in?
The one who looked at you once
because you got in her way.
Still, I could tell. She was into me.
Why don't you set us up?
Are you setting Ross up with someone?
Does she have a wedding dress?
Come on, I'm serious.
Okay, I'll do it, but as long as
you promise you won't marry her.
Fine, I..
What if she's the one?
Man, you have a problem.
Rachel?
I'm making up flyers to try
to get new massage clients.
Can I come to Bloomingdale's
and use the copier?
Sure, but they might think it's weird
since I don't work there anymore.
Oh, my God! What happened?
I got a job at Ralph Lauren.
Well, that's great! Congratulations!
A year ago.
You've lasted all year! Good for you.
You could still use the copier
where I actually work.
But come by at lunch
so my boss doesn't see you.
Kim will freak out.
She doesn't like me.
-I don't think my boss likes me.
-I don't think mine likes me.
Maybe it's a universal thing.
Maybe because you're all hanging
around here at 11:30 on a Wednesday.
Let's head off to work.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
You will not believe this.
I was making copies,
and Ralph Lauren came in.
Oh, my God. Did you talk to him?
A little. He seems really nice.
-Good kisser.
-What?
What?
-You kissed him?
-Totally.
Phoebe, are you serious?
He came in and introduced himself.
The next thing I know,
we're making out!
Phoebe, you do know he's married?
Phoebe.
I'm supposed to ask every guy
I make out with if he's married?
No, yeah, I should.
Hey, Joey.
Can I talk to you for a second?
There's a kid in this picture.
Do you know this kid?
Is it a relative?
No. I just thought it was cute.
That's what I was afraid of. Okay....
I really want you to feel
at home here, but...
some of this new stuff,
it's too girlie.
Like what?
Like this.
Pictures of cute babies we don't know.
We can't have that.
Joey, it's Anne Geddes.
She's a famous artist.
I don't know this baby. I don't know
if she's a famous artist or not.
I don't want to be a jerk, but
you're changing too much around here.
I'm sorry. I wanted to make
the place a little nicer.
But it's too much stuff.
You know, you got the candles and
the "foofy schmoofer" thing here.
Over here, you got
a picture of a watering can.
I just thought..
I'm sure it's a famous watering can.
But come on.
And what is with the really hot stick
in the bathroom?
It's a curling iron.
Well, that's okay then.
Okay, my towels, for instance.
I come into the bathroom...
and my towel is not on the floor,
where I keep it.
It's up here on some hook.
And it smells different.
-It's clean.
-It feels different.
It's dry.
All right, I can make my peace
with the clean, dry towels.
Also what is with
these chips you bought?
It's potpourri.
You're supposed to smell it.
Well, that's like summer in a bowl.
Kim, hi.
I handed in that marketing report, and
I never got to hear what you thought.
I didn't read it.
The spring line's really gonna be
great this year, huh?
I hear Ralph Lauren fooled around
with someone in the copy room.
Tell me everything.
Hey, guys.
What's up?
You know....
Oh, my God.
What happened to your teeth?
I whitened them.
Really?
What do you think?
I think I shouldn't look
directly at them.
Come on, seriously.
-They're really, really, really white.
-What was wrong with your old...
human teeth?
I did leave the gel on
a little longer than it said to.
-How much longer?
-A day.
Tonight is your date with Hillary.
I know. That's why I did it.
Are they really that bad?
You'll be fine.
Hillary's blind, right?
She will be after tonight.
Oh, Rach.
Do you notice anything..?
Your teeth?
Yes, I saw them from outside.
You guys are never gonna
believe this...
but Phoebe made out
with Ralph Lauren.
-What?
-Oh, my God!
She ran into him at my office,
and they just made out.
The craziest thing is,
now my boss likes me because...
it's the best gossip
she's heard all year.
I am proud of all my friends today.
I can't believe Phoebe made out
with Ralph Lauren.
I'm so jealous!
Hi, I'm Chandler,
your live-in boyfriend.
Chandler, please. Come on.
Look at him.
Well, I am no woman,
but that is one tasty dish.
Here.
Who's the silver fox?
That is your make-out buddy.
Don't you recognize him?
Oh, wait.
"Phoebe, I love you.
Kiss me, please."
That's not Ralph Lauren.
It sounds like him, though.
-What?
-Ralph doesn't look like that guy.
He's young, and he's got long hair
and a beard and a Hacky Sack..
Oh, my God. That's not Ralph Lauren.
That's Kenny the copy guy!
What?
I told my boss that someone
made out with Ralph Lauren.
If she finds out that I lied to her,
she'll hate me even more. Phoebe!
Why would the copy guy say
he's Ralph Lauren?
To get you to make out with him!
This will make them look less white.
Nope.
Colors that don't work are...
blue, yellow, green, red, black,
white, orange and purple.
Do you wanna try this highlighter again?
No, I think it poisoned me a little.
The date starts in an hour.
What am I'm gonna do?
Maybe if your skin was lighter,
your teeth wouldn't look so bright.
Oh, great! So all I need to do
is get some new skin. Thank you.
If we put just a little bit
of makeup on you..
Whoa!
We're not 13 anymore.
This is the only thing left
that has a shot at working.
Won't she notice I have makeup on?
Half the guys out there
have makeup on.
What?
Half the people.. I mean..
Just try it and see.
I am not putting on makeup.
Hello? Ross, could you put up
some of these flyers for me?
No! Demon! Demon!
Our drawers will smell nice, and
we didn't waste these pantyhose.
God forbid we throw out old underwear.
You know what?
I'm gonna go over to Joey's.
We've got to organize
the wrapping paper.
I've really gotten in touch with
my feminine side enough today.
In fact, we're two sachets away
from becoming a lesbian couple.
This has been a girlie day.
You're right. I'm sorry.
I just feel like I need
to be in a "guy" place...
do kind of a "man" thing.
You go over to Joey's and...
drink some beer and
hammer up some dry wall.
When guys hang out, they don't just
drink beer and hammer up dry wall.
When girls hang out, we don't have
pillow fights in our underwear.
I'm sorry. We do.
I don't know why I said that.
Hey, Chandler.
Come on in.
We're knitting potholders.
No, thanks, Josephine.
Ross, I was wondering if..
Oh, my God! Where are all the men?
-Hi, Kim.
-Hi, Rachel.
Remember what happened yesterday?
Well, it didn't happen.
You didn't cancel the fabric order?
Okay, two things didn't happen.
Remember I told you someone
made out with Ralph Lauren?
Well, it turns out that's not true.
It's not true?
That's interesting.
Because I checked. Only one keycard
was used to access the copier...
yesterday during lunch, and
that keycard belonged to you.
You think I made out with him?
Listen to me...
sleeping with Ralph is not
gonna get you my job.
I don't want your job. I don't.
This is a mistake.
I didn't make out with him.
Nobody made out with him.
I didn't use my keycard yesterday.
I don't even know
how to use my keycard.
-Hi, Ralph.
-Hi, Kim.
Yeah. Nothing happened.
You could cut the sexual tension
in here with a knife.
After that, what could I do
except become a chef?
Soon, I hope to open
my own restaurant.
You're a really great listener.
Most guys I go out with,
they talk and talk.
It's like, "Shut your mouth."
You know?
I've been talking too much.
Why don't we talk about you?
Come on, I want to know.
Okay. I'm from Long lsland.
I came to the city for college.
I have a 5-year-old son,
and in my spare time...
I like to read spy novels.
But let's talk more about you.
If you sear the stems of the flowers
first in a frying pan...
your arrangement will
look fresh much longer.
Joey, that is such a great tip!
Monica, I need to talk
to the girl with the flowers.
Okay, but I'm gonna teach you
how to make a bird feeder...
out of a pine cone
and some peanut butter.
I love birds.
What is the matter with you?
-What?
-You're arranging flowers!
You got dead flowers!
You've got a picture of a baby
dressed like flowers!
This is not Joey!
Look, I am still Joey, okay?
Flowers, they're just nice to look at.
And that happens to be a picture
by a famous artist of a famous baby.
You're turning into a woman.
No, I'm not.
Why would you say that?
That's just mean.
Now I've upset you? What did I say?
It's not what you said.
It's the way you said it.
Oh, my God!
I'm a woman!
So now she thinks that I made out
with him to get her job.
-Why didn't you just tell the truth?
-I did.
She doesn't think anyone would confuse
Kenny the copy guy with Ralph Lauren.
What if Kenny were the real brains
behind the whole company?
What if Kenny hired that Ralph guy
to be the pretty front man, huh?
Did she ever think of that?
You were with Kenny today.
Just for a second.
Phoebe, what am I gonna do?
The only thing you can do.
Sleep with him.
I'm not gonna sleep with him.
I mean, I could, but I wouldn't.
Sleep with Kenny.
-That wouldn't help me.
-Oh, yes, it would.
I've had a really good time tonight.
I rarely connect with someone
this much on the first date.
Me neither.
I've had a really
good time too, you know.
Are you gonna eat that bread?
I just like the smell.
You make me laugh.
Would you like to move to the couch?
Maybe I'll just turn down
the lights a little?
How about all the way?
Okay.
Wow, cool poster.
Or should I say, "groovy poster"?
So...
where were we?
Are those your teeth?
You can see them, huh?
Yes. They're insanely white.
I did that for you.
What's the matter with you?
What's the matter with me?
You've got a black light. It's 1999!
Oh, good. Kim, hi.
Hi, Rachel. I wanted to ask you, have
you seen the new Ralph Lauren sheets?
What am I thinking?
Of course you have.
Okay, look.
I'm sorry that I lied to you before.
You were right. Ralph and I were
an item, but we're not anymore.
Oh, really?
Yeah, he dumped me.
He said, "Rachel, I can't do this.
Even though you're a very, very...
very beautiful woman...
I can't do this.
I'm married and I'm sorry."
But he said,
"And you will never get promoted...
especially not above Kim,
who is an integral cog...
in the Ralph Lauren machine."
You expect me to believe..
-Hi, Ralph.
-Hi, Kim.
Oh, my God.
He gave you the coldest look I've
ever seen. It's like he hates you!
Then it is true!
Of course it's true.
And it hurts so bad.
Oh, honey, come here.
Oh, it'll be okay.
We've all been there.
You and Ralph?
Kenny the copy boy.
-I need to talk to you.
-What's the matter? You upset?
Would you like me to get
a pint of ice cream and two spoons?
No, no, no ice cream. Look....
We gotta get rid of all
this girlie stuff in here.
I gotta be a man!
The living room has to
remain a guy place, okay?
That's the way it has to be.
I'll just put it all in my room.
Good. Great.
Thanks for being so understanding.
I didn't want to make
a big deal out of this.
But you could put the picture
of the famous baby in my room.
I mean, if you want to.
Okay.
And maybe the watering can there.
Sure.
And a couple of these
little tiny boxes.
Joey, do you want me to put
it all in your room?
Okay.